<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://umass-cs-326.github.io/blog</id>
    <title>COMPSCI 326 Blog</title>
    <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
    <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://umass-cs-326.github.io/blog"/>
    <subtitle>COMPSCI 326 Blog</subtitle>
    <icon>https://umass-cs-326.github.io/img/favicon.png</icon>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Welcome to Web Programming!]]></title>
        <id>welcome</id>
        <link href="https://umass-cs-326.github.io/blog/welcome"/>
        <updated>2023-02-06T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We are thrilled to have you onboard and look forward to a challenging and enriching journey as we dive into the exciting world of web programming.]]></summary>
        <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We are thrilled to have you onboard and look forward to a challenging and enriching journey as we dive into the exciting world of web programming.</p><p>By the end of this course, you will gain a fundamental understanding of web development and be able to use both front-end and back-end technologies to build stunning web applications. In particular, you will learn to create stunning designs and user experiences with HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.</p><p>There are several reasons why taking this course is essential for your career, both in industry and in graduate school. Here are five:</p><ol><li>Understand the latest trends in web programming: Knowing the latest web technologies will help you create and develop modern web applications that meet the latest standards in web design and usability.</li><li>Master coding and problem-solving skills: With a deep understanding of the concepts, you can effectively code and solve programming problems to complete complex tasks.</li><li>Improve job opportunities: Your web programming knowledge can provide valuable skills for landing great job opportunities.</li><li>Understand how the web works: With an in-depth knowledge of the underlying principles and how they apply to the real world, you can better understand how the web works.</li><li>Learn important development processes: Knowing the essential development processes will make you more productive and ensure the development of higher quality web applications.</li></ol><p>So, what are you waiting for? Get started on this journey with us and begin mastering web programming!</p><p>We are looking forward to teaching you the foundations of web programming and to equipping you with the necessary tools and skills to succeed!</p>]]></content>
        <author>
            <name>Tim Richards</name>
            <uri>https://timdrichards.github.io</uri>
        </author>
        <category label="welcome" term="welcome"/>
    </entry>
</feed>